<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kevin McGowan&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kevin McGowan&#39;s Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 20:21:15 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kevin-mcgowan.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 20:21:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi my name is Kevin and I make stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tangible HTML</title>
      <link>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 20:21:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/thesis/</guid>
      <description>The thesis project is the culmination of the Media Arts and Practice program. My project, entitled Tangible HTML explores new methods of teaching coding for the web. For a quick description, read the Abstract below; keep reading for a thorough write up. Or just skip ahead to the documentation video if you’re a visual learner…
Abstract  In this increasingly complex technical age, the ability to write code is becoming evermore significant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the news</title>
      <link>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/blog/in-the-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 18:29:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/blog/in-the-news/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend The School of Cinematic Arts published an Alumni Profile about my post graduation experience, enjoy the first paragraph below or find the full article on the SCA website.
Kevin McGowan graduated among the first cohort of the Media Arts+Practice division at the USC School of Cinematic Arts in May 2017. A life-long Trojan fan from Palos Verdes, McGowan always aspired to attending SCA. However, the MA+P program was a surprise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London and Paris</title>
      <link>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/blog/london-and-paris/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 18:27:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/blog/london-and-paris/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s now a week after returning from Europe. London is AMAZING, I so desperately want to live there at some point in my life, at least have a second home there. Luckily this year, my mum did not make us go to all the famous land marks that typically make up the city. This trip was spent mainly at contemporary locations around the city and historical place just outside. We did a tour at Oxford University day 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thesis Documentation</title>
      <link>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/work/thesis-documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 20:18:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/work/thesis-documentation/</guid>
      <description>This is the video presentation of my senior thesis entitled, Tangible HTML.For a quick understanding of the project enjoy the video below, for a more thorough read into the project please visit my Thesis page.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graduation at last!</title>
      <link>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/blog/graduation-at-last/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 18:27:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/blog/graduation-at-last/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday was college graduation! The feeling like theres no more school left feels odd, it probably really won&amp;rsquo;t hit me until September when classes start back up for my friends. The day was spectacular, I had Will Ferrel tell me he will always love me thru song, Hillary and Bill Clinton were at the ceremony for cinematic arts. After getting my diploma holder, with no diploma in it of course, I walked off stage right past them, needless to say, they smiled at me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Almost There</title>
      <link>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/blog/almost-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 18:27:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/blog/almost-there/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s now Tuesday May 2nd. The thesis showcase is in 6 days and the project is almost&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; there. Not really though. It seems as though with every step of the process I have to spend more money and more time on things I budgeted as being far less in the beginning. I&amp;rsquo;m grateful I spent all the time to plan it out, but this being my first real, large project, I was of course wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playing with RFID</title>
      <link>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/blog/playing-with-rfid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 18:27:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/blog/playing-with-rfid/</guid>
      <description>The thesis project is in full swing now as the various tech starts to arrive for production. The groundwork has been set and its soldering time. In total some 10 RFID sensor chips will be set up in an array to read all of the blocks played in the playground. I have luckily found a library that will make interfacing with the chip extremely easy, and interfacing with all at once should be no more difficult than 2 in sync.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thesis Design Brief</title>
      <link>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/blog/thesis-design-brief/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 18:26:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/blog/thesis-design-brief/</guid>
      <description>To reach the ultimate goal of this project took an awful lot of &amp;lsquo;soul searching&amp;rsquo; would be the best estimate I could give. I approached the assignment by creating lists of things that interested me; these included things such as building physical object, anything BIG, and lots of coding involved. Combined these are aspects that would end up creating a project that I would enjoy working on and would hopefully be revolutionary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mapping Music</title>
      <link>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/work/mapping-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 20:34:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/work/mapping-music/</guid>
      <description>Following my love of music and passion for visualizing data, I have created a tool that is used to create unique visualizations of any song that is brought into the program. Inspired by Casey Reas&amp;rsquo;s work, I built a program of objects and rules. All objects have a form and a simple set of rules. An example includes form no. 1: A circle that tries to move away from all other circles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rubens Tube</title>
      <link>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/work/rubens-tube/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2014 21:40:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kevin-mcgowan.com/work/rubens-tube/</guid>
      <description>Built as my final project of freshman year, the rubens tube was designed as a crossover project from a traditional physics experiment to a contemporary art piece. In physics, the rubens tube is a simple experiment made for visualizing sound waves with fire. It, at its most basic aspect, is a BBQ with a speaker attached. As the speaker creates sound, the pressure in the tube fluctuates based off of the sound waves.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>